{
    "Title": "15 Minutes With",
    "BannerName": "Caroline Lemblé",
    "Tagline": "Meet one of the freelance stylists in Berlin",
    "Time": "14.35 Berlin",
    "ChatText": "we met caroline for a walk in berlin.",
    "IntroText": "The French Caroline Lemblé is currently living in Berlin together with her dog Lou. In the past, she has worked for Harper’s Bazaar, Interview and L’Officiel and is now a freelance stylist. Her impressive resumé is an homage to her hard work, dedication and love for fashion.",
    
    "Question_section1":
    {
        "Time_one": "14.40 Berlin",
        "LeftQuestion":
        [
            {
                "question": "What does time mean to you?",
                "answer": "Time is very precious to me. Often we don’t have enough and hurry from one appointment to the next. It’s important to make time for the people that matter."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who or what is the essence of beauty to you?",
                "answer": "Beauty is carried in the heart. You can often see the good nature of people in their eyes. They always have this certain kind of warmth to them."
            },
            {
                "question": "Latest discovery?",
                "answer": "Café Dots in Neukölln."
            }
        ],
        "RightQuestion":
        [
            {
                "question": "What is your morning routine?",
                "answer": "Cigarettes and coffee and then taking my dog Lou for a walk in my Pajamas."
            },
            {
                "question": "Favorite spot in Berlin?",
                "answer": "Plänterwald forest – a beautiful small forest, 10 mins away from my apartment."
            },
            {
                "question": "On sundays I…",
                "answer": "I don’t do anything on Sundays. I sleep in, don’t read any mails, no calls… dosing in bed and watching a good movie in the evening."
            }
        ]
    },
    "QuoteText": "It’s important to make time for the people that matter.",
    "Name": "Caroline",
    "CenterQuestion":
    {
       "question": "what do you like to do when you have a day off?",
       "answer": "Coffee to go at the Pavillon and then a walk through the forest."
        
    },
    "Question_section2":
    {
        "Time_two": "14.45 Berlin",
        "LeftQuestion":
        [
            {
                "question": "What’s your favorite memory?",
                "answer": "My childhood in Morocco, Loveparade in 2000, my university time at the Academy of Fashion and Design, and the vacations with my mother."
            }
        ],
        "RightQuestion":
        [
            {
                "question": "Who or what inspired you in life and why?",
                "answer": "My mom, she’s one of a kind and has always done her thing."
            }
        ]
    },
    "WatchSection":
    {
       "FavoriteWatch": "favorite watch",
       "WatchText": "The Tribeca in white – black, small and fashionable",
       "CheckThisWatch": "CHECK THIS WATCH",
       "ProductName": "The Tribeca",
       "ProductShortDesc": "White - Black"
    },
    "Question_section3":
    {
        "Time_three": "14.50 Berlin",
        "LeftQuestion":
        [
            {
                "question": "What people do not know about you?",
                "answer": "I collect china figures, like an old grandma."
            },
            {
                "question": "I’m always late/on time...",
                "answer": "I’m always on time. Why? Out of respect."
            },
            {
                "question": "In five years time I…",
                "answer": "In five years... hopefully run a small hotel in Greece."
            }

        ],
        "RightQuestion":
        [
            {
                "question": "Where would you want to be beamed to right this moment?",
                "answer": "Mykonos, I have spent one of my best holidays there together with my best friend."
            },
            {
                "question": "Gold or silver?",
                "answer": "Silver."
            }
        ]
    },
    "MainCloseImageText":
    {
       "MainText": "15 Minutes",
       "QuoteText": "I’m always on time. Why? Out of respect."
    }

}